<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>News &amp; Updates - Weld 2020 - new site</title>
    <description/>
    <link>http://www.weld2020.org/news_updates</link>
    <item>
      <title>Press Release: Governor Bill Weld heads to New Hampshire this Weekend</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boston, MA Governor Bill Weld will be touring diners in Western New Hampshire on Saturday, May 11th, followed by a Town Hall in White River, Vermont. “As a native of neighboring Massachusetts, I know that New Hampshire voters pick Presidents and they want to get up close and personal with their candidates,” said Weld. “I look forward to meeting Republican primary voters and explaining why we need honorable, Reaganesque leadership in the White House.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tour is Weld’s first visit to Western New Hampshire during the 2020 campaign. Governor Weld will discuss Donald Trump’s continued Nixonian lawlessness. He also looks forward to explaining his positive vision for an inclusive Republican Party that takes on the real challenges facing America.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All events are open press.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Saturday, May 11th&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Diner Tour&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:00 AM: The Lebanon Diner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;24 Hanover Street &lt;br&gt;Lebanon, NH 03766&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:45 AM: Shyrl’s Diner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;31 Main Street&lt;br&gt;West Lebanon, NH 03784&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12:30 PM: Four Aces Diner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;23 Bridge Street&lt;br&gt;West Lebanon, NH 03784&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Town Hall hosted by Vermont Digger and the Lebanon Valley News&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3:00 PM: Hartford High School Gymnasium&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;37 Highland Avenue &lt;br&gt;White River Junction, VT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Tim Wayne</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/press_release_governor_bill_weld_heads_to_new_hampshire_this_weekend</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press Release: Gov. Bill Weld Answers RNC Chair’s Question About Why Any Republican Would Run Against “This Guy”</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boston I am not surprised to learn that Robert Mueller notified AG Barr that his 4-page letter to Congress mischaracterized “the context, nature, and substance” of the report.  The second volume of the special counsel’s report clearly laid out the case for multiple occasions of obstruction of justice by the President.AG Barr has erred in both his opinion that the President could not be indicted and in his clear attempt to frame a narrative that favors and protects the President.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;The 2000 opinion by the Office of Legal Counsel, whose job description is to give advice to the President personally, did not take into consideration that the U.S. Constitution says that a President remains liable to indictment, prosecution and punishment after he leaves office.This Constitutional provision would be rendered meaningless if a President could totally and permanently escape indictment simply by being re-elected, which would allow him to coast past the five-year statute of limitations for federal crimes.It almost seems that the Attorney General took insufficient account of the unanimous 1974 decision of the United States Supreme Court in United States vs. Nixon, holding that the President of the United States is notabove the law.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;No man is above the law.  Our nation is built on the principle that we are all equal before Lady Justice, including the President of the United States. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Given the evidence laid out by Mr. Mueller, had I been in his place, I would have pursued an indictment of the President of the United States for obstruction of Justice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 12:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Bill Weld for President 2020</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/gov_bill_weld_answers_rnc_chair_s_question_about_why_any_republican_would_run_against_this_guy</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press Release: Bill Weld on Mueller Report: Donald Trump is a one-man crime wave</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boston, MA This morning, Republican Presidential candidate and former Massachusetts, Governor Bill Weld weighed in on the Mueller Report in an appearance on MSNBC with Stephanie Ruhle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This man is a one-man crime wave,” he said. “He instructed senior legal officials, senior national security, senior intelligence officials to lie, he actively sought out and suborned perjury. That is obstruction of justice and the President is fortunate that in substance Bob Mueller gave him a mulligan."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Weld continued, “The House should have a full airing of everything that Mr. Mueller found...The last thing that Mr. Mueller said in the report was to charge the President you would need evidence of corrupt intent. What would be evidence of corrupt intent? Well, if the President tried to limit or stop investigation of him or his family to avoid embarrassment or criminal exposure, that would be massive evidence of criminal intent. Well, that’s exactly what the 60 previous pages of the report demonstrated.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener" href="https://www.msnbc.com/stephanie-ruhle/watch/did-the-mueller-report-change-bill-weld-s-plan-for-2020-1499605059965" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="https://d3n8a8pro7vhmx.cloudfront.net/weld2020/pages/64/attachments/original/1555964067/blog_bill-weld-and-stephanie-ruhle2.jpg?1555964067" alt="Bill Weld on Mueller Report: Donald Trump is a one-man crime wave" width="617" height="350"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener" href="https://www.msnbc.com/stephanie-ruhle/watch/did-the-mueller-report-change-bill-weld-s-plan-for-2020-1499605059965" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See the entire interview here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill Weld was appointed to the Department of Justice by President Ronald Reagan, where he served for seven years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 03:36:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Bill Weld for President 2020</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/bill_weld_on_mueller_report_donald_trump_is_a_one_man_crime_wave</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press Release: Governor Bill Weld Releases Statement on Mueller Report</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;"Confidence in our leaders and in our institutions is at the heart of our democracy. That confidence has been shaken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It is essential that Special Counsel Bob Mueller come before Congress and address the validity of his report that has been redacted and released. Is this the report he issued? Are these the conclusions to which he came or has the report been altered in any way? Was he pressured to remove or change anything?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I resigned from the Justice Department in 1988 when I felt strongly that the actions of the Justice Department betrayed the confidence of the American people and threatened confidence in our institutions and rule of law. It is long past time for those in positions of authority to similarly stand up and take action. No American and no President is above the law and can attempt to obstruct justice without consequence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I have known Bob Mueller for over 30 years and I have every confidence in his ability and his integrity."&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 23:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Bill Weld for President 2020</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/pr_governor_bill_weld_releases_statement_on_mueller_report</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Great environmentalist' Weld dives into race against Trump</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener" href="https://www.eenews.net/stories/1060178757" target="_blank"&gt;E&amp;amp;E News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img style="background-color: transparent; border: 1px solid #ffffff; font-size: 13px; margin: 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; box-sizing: border-box; width: 940px; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;" src="https://www.eenews.net/image_assets/2019/04/image_asset_52599.jpg" alt="Bill Weld. Photo credit: Keiki Hiromi/Polaris/Newscom" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="caption" style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 12px; margin: 5px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #666666; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;Fomer Massachusetts Gov. Bill Weld, seen here in a February file photo, wants to challenge President Trump for the Republican presidential nomination. &lt;span class="credit" style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 11px; margin: 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #999999; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;Keiki Hiromi/Polaris/Newscom&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 14px; margin: 1em 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;On a clear summer day in 1996, Massachusetts Gov. William Weld (R) signed the Rivers Protection Act, an aggressive environmental policy that put a development buffer around the state's rivers and creeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 14px; margin: 1em 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;"For each new development anywhere along our riverbanks, this bill requires proof that the project will not harm the environment and that no feasible alternative exists," he said, standing in Boston next to the Charles River, which was improving from decades of industrial pollution but which still had a brown tint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 14px; margin: 1em 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;Weld, fully clothed, then celebrated by diving into the river behind him, followed shortly by state Sen. Robert Durand (D), who wrote the bill and shepherded it through the state Legislature as a key committee chairman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 14px; margin: 1em 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;"It actually surprised me that he went in, so I went in after him," Durand, who has since retired from elective office, recalled during a recent interview with E&amp;amp;E News.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 14px; margin: 1em 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;This week, Weld took another dive, making official his long-shot candidacy in the 2020 presidential election as the only Republican challenging President Trump in the primary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 14px; margin: 1em 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;His swim in the Charles lives on as an example of his showmanship, a key quality if Weld hopes to have a chance against Trump, a real estate mogul and former reality television star.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="background-color: transparent; border: 0px; font-size: 14px; margin: 1em 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: #000000; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-variant-caps: normal; font-weight: normal; letter-spacing: normal; orphans: auto; text-align: start; text-indent: 0px; text-transform: none; white-space: normal; widows: auto; word-spacing: 0px; -webkit-text-size-adjust: auto; text-decoration: none; background-position: initial initial; background-repeat: initial initial;"&gt;But people who worked with Weld say diving into the river was also a sign of how seriously he takes environmental policies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Timothy Cama</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/_great_environmentalist_weld_dives_into_race_against_trump</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press Release: Governor Bill Weld Presents Remarks at World Affairs Council of New Hampshire</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boston, MA Governor Bill Weld will deliver an important foreign policy address at the World Affairs Council of New Hampshire titled “What Role Should America Play in the World Today?” Governor Weld will lay out a vision for a positive, unifying approach to America’s relationship with nations around the World.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://d3n8a8pro7vhmx.cloudfront.net/weld2020/pages/66/attachments/original/1555966966/blog_world-affairs-council-new-hampshire.jpg?1555966966" alt="blog_world-affairs-council-new-hampshire.jpg" width="617" height="350"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:56:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Bill Weld for President 2020</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/governor_bill_weld_presents_remarks_at_world_affairs_council_of_new_hampshire</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press Release: Bill Weld Announces Candidacy For President Of The United States of America</title>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;&lt;em&gt;“It is time for patriotic women and men across our great nation to stand and plant a flag.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boston, MA (April 15, 2019) Today Governor Bill Weld announced his candidacy to run for President of the United States of America in the Republican Primary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ours is a nation built on courage, resilience, and independence. In these times of great political strife, when both major parties are entrenched in their “win at all cost” battles, the voices of the American people are being ignored and our nation is suffering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is time for patriotic men and women across our great nation to stand and plant a flag. It is time to return to the principles of Lincoln – equality, dignity, and opportunity for all. There is no greater cause on earth than to preserve what truly makes America great. I am ready to lead that fight,” said Weld.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener" href="https://www.cnn.com/videos/tv/2019/04/15/lead-gov-bill-weld-2020-announcement-live-jake-tapper.cnn" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="https://d3n8a8pro7vhmx.cloudfront.net/weld2020/pages/65/attachments/original/1555963983/blog_weld-on-jake-tapper2.jpg?1555963983" alt="blog_weld-on-jake-tapper2.jpg" width="617" height="350"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the months ahead Bill Weld will go directly to the American people to talk about their concerns, priorities, and dreams – both for themselves and for their children. He will share his vision of an America that lifts up all people, that unlocks the potential of every student, every small business owner, and every American worker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Reagan Republican who was appointed US Attorney by President Ronald Reagan, Bill Weld knows that America can still be that “shining city on a hill.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill Weld believes that we must preserve the democratic institutions of our Republic: the rule of law, a free and open press, and America’s global leadership in maintaining a freer, safer world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He believes that transparency is the cornerstone of accountability, that freedom dies in darkness, and that government must serve the people, not the politicians.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bill Weld is uniquely qualified to serve the American people as President. He has an unblemished record of service and leadership. In addition to seven years in the Department of Justice, he served two terms as Governor in Massachusetts, where he was reelected by the largest margin in state history. He cut taxes 21 times, never raised them, balanced the budget, and oversaw six upgrades in the state’s bond rating. He signed landmark welfare reform, established public education standards, and was a trailblazer as an early proponent for LGBT civil rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was ranked the most fiscally conservative Governor in the country by the Cato Institute and the Wall Street Journal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Governor Weld was born in Smithtown, NY. He is a graduate of Harvard College summa cum laude, studied international economics at University College, Oxford, and received his law degree from Harvard Law School cum laude. Bill is an active member of the Council on Foreign Relations and of the InterAction Council, an organization of former heads of state who meet around the world and issue annual reports on international issues of transcendent importance such as nuclear proliferation, religious sectarianism, and food and water. Bill served by Presidential appointment on the U.S. Holocaust Memorial Council.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He and his wife, Leslie, live in Canton, MA. Between them, they have eight children and eight grandchildren.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Weld 2020</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/bill_weld_announces_candidacy_for_president_of_the_united_states_of_america</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Republican Running Against Trump in 2020</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Running in a primary election against a sitting President is, generally speaking, a futile effort. To come up with a plausible primary challenge, you’ve got to think back pretty far, maybe to 1980, when Edward Kennedy challenged President Jimmy Carter for the Democratic nomination—and even then Kennedy failed. But just about everything in the Presidency of Donald Trump has been unprecedented, so we shouldn’t be very surprised to see something unusual in the 2020 campaign. And it looks like Bill Weld is going to run against Donald Trump to become the Republican nominee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There aren’t many Republicans like Bill Weld in national politics these days. Weld is a lawyer and a former Justice Department official, and he served as governor of Massachusetts for much of the nineteen-nineties. In 2016, he ran as Vice-President on the Libertarian Party ticket. He’s a New England moderate—that is, fiscally conservative and socially liberal. But Weld is not at all moderate in his views on Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.newyorker.com/news/the-new-yorker-interview/bill-weld-the-republican-planning-to-run-against-trump-in-2020"&gt;Read article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Weld 2020</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/the_republican_running_against_trump_in_2020</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Moderate Republican Wants to Give Donald Trump a Primary Challenge in 2020</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style="float: left; margin-right: 15px;" src="https://d3n8a8pro7vhmx.cloudfront.net/weld2020/pages/63/attachments/original/1555804632/icon-sound.png?1555804632" alt="icon-sound.png" width="40" height="33" /&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wnyc.org/story/moderate-republican-wants-primary-donald-trump-2020-pm/"&gt;Listen to interview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump boasts an approval rating among Republican voters of close to ninety per cent. But the former Massachusetts governor Bill Weld recently announced an exploratory committee to challenge Trump in the primary. It looks like a political suicide mission, but Weld sees a pathway to victory that runs through his neighboring state of New Hampshire, to other blue-leaning states where Republican voters might be open to a different candidate for the nomination. Weld is a type of Republican rarely seen at the national level these days—a New England moderate—and he’s called Trump’s Presidency a “train wreck.” He says that some “billionaires” will back his long-shot bid, and he’s betting that the damage from investigations may end Trump’s charmed political life. Weld criticizes the white-supremacist dog whistles used in Trump’s 2016 campaign, and he calls Republicans in Washington victims of Stockholm syndrome—identifying with the man who captured their party.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Weld 2020</author>
      <link>http://www.weld2020.org/a_moderate_republican_wants_to_give_donald_trump_a_primary_challenge_in_2020</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
